SHRADDHA PANDEY

HRIS ANALYST AT SHAW COMMUNICATIONS (CALGARY, CANADA)

DESIGNATION

Hris analyst

ROLE

SUBJECT MATTER EXPERT TECHNICAL SUPPORT

123 CALGARY STREET CALGARY, CANADA, ST 12345

SHRADDHA.PANDEY2301@GMAIL.COM

INTRODUCTION

Intermediate professional HR Administration experience in Payroll, Benefits and HRIS;

Canadian Payroll Association qualification -Payroll Compliance Practitioner (PCP Certification.

DEVELOP AND SUPPORT THE TESTING ND IMPLEMENTATION OF INTEGRATIONS OUT OF AND INTO THE HR SYSTEM.

CONDUCTED SEVERAL DATA INTEGRITY AUDITS

RESPONSIBLE FOR TYHE CONFIGURATIOBN AND ADMINISTRATIONS

.

EXPERIENCE

SHAW COMMUNICATION, CALGARY, ALBERTA, CANADA — HRIS ANALYST

JANUARY 2013 - JUNE 2018

SAMSUNG, TORONTO, CANADA — HRIS ANALYST

JULY2009 - DECEMBER 2012

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO, CANADA — BACHELORS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

AUGUST 2005 - JUNE 2009

Founded in 1827, the University of Toronto has evolved into Canada's leading institution of learning, discovery and knowledge creation. We are proud to be one of the world's top research-intensive universities, driven to invent and innovate

DPS, NEW DELHI -10+2

MARCH 2003 - MARCH 2005

GNNPS, GORAKHPUR - PRIMARY AND SECONDARY EDUCATION.

PROJECTS

WEB OPTIMIZATION —

- 1. Personal Information Management
 - 2. Personal Training Management
 - 3. Recruitment Process Management
 - 4. Project Management

The information collected through the above activities will be maintained in a centralized server and could be accessed through the Internet.

SKILLS

HRIS software, including PeopleSoft HRMS or HCM and Crystal Reports.

Certifications

- Cloud Connect for Third Party Payroll
- Workday Advance Studio
- Workday Integration Core

AWARDS

BEST EMPLOYEE AWARD IN 2012.

BEST PROJECT AWARD IN 2016.

LANGUAGES

HINDI, ENGLISH, FRENCH

INDUSTRY

IT AND INFRASTRUCTURE.

The company has decided to create a corporate intranetwork to connect all offices and their network would also be utilized in case of implementation. The information collected through this management and process related activities are maintained as folios.